

PERSONAL DETAILS

Full Name:

Amarakoon Mudhiyanselage Milinda Anuradha Sanka Amarakoon

Date Of Birth: 1997 January 31

Gender: Male

Civil Status: Single

Nationality: Sri Lankan

NIC Number: 970312153V

CONTACT DETAILS

Email:

manuradhasanka@gmail.com

Phone: 0713100963

Website: www.codemeets.com
Github: github.com/milindasanka
Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/milinda-anuradha-sanka-619132131

SKILLS

Programming Languages:

- PHP
- JavaScript
- Dart
- C#
- Java
- C++ and C

MILINDA ANURADHA SANKA AMARAKOON

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a Software Engineer with around 3 years of experience in the industry and having experience as a Software Engineer. I am working on Laravel, php, Wordpress, Flutter and JavaScript as primary technologies. I am preferred with both SQL and NoSQL. I am also working on solution designing for software projects including UI/UX perspectives while making sure milestones are achieved in incremental manner.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

E wings Solutions | 2022 - Present

- Backend development with php, Laravel and mysql
- Mobile application development with Flutter SDK
- Web Development using Codeigniter and php, Javascript
- Chrome Extension Development using Javascript
- Server Management Nginx and Apache

Associate Software Engineer

Coderay Technologies | 2021 - 2022

- Mobile application development with Flutter SDK
- Backend development with Node js, MySQL and Firebase
- Backend web development with Laravel.
- Software Testing (Web Front-end and API)
- WHM and Cpanel Server Management

Junior Software Engineer

Coderay Technologies | 2020 - 2021

- Full stack web development of the ERP Platform.
- front end applications using Laravel, Bootstrap
- Research and development related to Barcode Generation
- Develop and maintain Moodle websites and WordPress Websites.

EDUCATION HISTORY

SIBA Campus Sri Lanka

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology) | 2022 - 2023

Sri Lanka Institute of Advanced Technological Education, (SLIATE)

Higher National Diploma in Information Technology - (HNDIT) | 2018 - 2021

SITC Campus

Diploma in Cyber Security & Ethical Hacking | 2023

Tools, Libraries and OS's:

- Laravel
- Flutter
- Codelgniter
- Node
- Shell
- Git
- Nginx Server
- Apache Server
- HTML
- CSS
- jQuery
- Jira
- Windows
- Linux
- Mac
- Putty
- FileZilla
- cPanel
- WordPress
- Postman

Database Technologies:

- MySQL
- Firebase
- Microsoft SQL Server

REASERCH AND PROJECTS

Instamart Shopping Website

Technologies : Laravel, php, Javascript, Flutter, Payment Gateway

TravelGo Hotel Website

Technologies: Laravel Web Framework and php, Javascript, Sql

PC NET Shopping Website

Technologies: php, Javascript, Sql, html, bootstrap,css

Rhythm Windows Music Player software engineering project

Technologies: C#

Codemeets.com my personal blog

Technologies: WordPress, Cpanal, Google Ads

Principia Institute Management Systerm

Technologies: Laravel Backend Html Css Fronten and MySql.

Nursing Premier

Technologies: Html, Css, JavaScript.

Chrome Extension

Technologies: Html, JavaScript, ChromeScript, API

EXTRA CURICULER ACTIVITIES

- All island School Music Cometition Encounter 2009, 2015
- Member of the School Scince Club
- Member of the School Football Team
- Participation in 2006 English Camp
- Possess Driving License

REFEREES

Mr. I. P. Jeewantha Madubashana

Head / Lecture Srilanka Institute Of Senior Software Engineer

Advanced Technological Education Mitra Innovation

Tel: +94 71 833 5525 Tel: +94 71 487 4141

I hereby declare that the details furnished above are true and correct to the best of my knowledge

Date	Signature